<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Cave</string>
    <string name="die">Die</string>
    <string name="beenBefore">What will you do?</string>
    <string name="cont">\*Continue\*</string>

    <string name="StoryIntro1">You wake up inside what appears to be some kind of cave.
    You sit and wonder for a while. You have no idea how you got here. All you can remember
    is your name. What was that again?</string>

    <string name="StoryIntro2">Aaah yes, that was it: %1$s! Right then %1$s, you\'re in a bit of
    a sticky situation here. What are you going to do first?</string>

    <string name="StartOption1">Stand up and look around</string>
    <string name="StartOption2">Pat around to see what you can find</string>
    <string name="StartOption3">Lay down and cry</string>

    <string name="Track1Intro">See, that would have been a smart idea if it wasn\'t so
        dark in here! You can\'t see anything, what\'s your next move?</string>

    <string name="Track1StartOption1">Fumble around and find a wall</string>
    <string name="Track1StartOption2">Pat around to see what you can find</string>
    <string name="Track1StartOption3">Squint your eyes and look harder</string>


    <string name ="Track1Option1story">You fumble through the pitch black. A stench of damp and decay
    rises up into your nostrils. Wherever you are, it\'s not a good place to be. You eventually find a
    wall. What next?</string>

    <string name="Track1_1_1">Try to break through the wall</string>
    <string name="Track1_1_2">Pat around to see what you can find</string>
    <string name="Track1_1_3">Scream for help</string>

    <string name ="Track1_1_1story">You pound against the cold, slimy wall like your life depends on it (it might do)
     but to no avail. There\'s no give. You\'re going to have to try something else!</string>

    <string name="Track1_1_1_1">Give up</string>
    <string name="Track1_1_1_2">Pat around to see what you can find (Take the hint)</string>
    <string name="Track1_1_1_3">Scream for help</string>


    <string name="Track2Intro">It appears that your suspicions were correct, %1$s, you ARE in a cave! Other than a solitary
        rock, you find little of interest.</string>

    <string name="Track2StartOption1">Pick up the rock</string>
    <string name="Track2StartOption2">Try something else</string>

    <string name="Track2_1_0">You pull the rock but it doesn\'t come away from the ground.
    Instead, it moves about an inch or so towards you before stopping abruptly. You hear a faint click.
    Much to your amazement, a wall some way ahead of you appears to slide away, revealing a dim light in the distance.
    I hope you\'re alone in here, because the screeching of the wall as it slid away would have awoken anyone&#8230;</string>

    <string name="Track2_1_1">Find somewhere to hide</string>
    <string name="Track2_1_2">\"Hello?\"</string>
    <string name="Track2_1_3">Follow the light</string>

    <string name="Milestone1BadEndingHiddenIntro">In the darkness it\'s difficult to see where would be
    best to hide, but in your infinite wisdom you crouch down by a wall. You are repulsed by the stench as slime
    from the walls drips down onto your head and neck. In the distance, but getting louder, you hear what sounds
    like foot prints. \"Maybe it\'s a big friendly giant\" \- You think to yourself.</string>

    <string name="Milestone1BadEnding">In the distance, but getting louder, you hear what sounds
    like foot prints. \"Maybe it\'s a big friendly giant\" \- You think to yourself.</string>

    <string name="m1be_1">Remain %1$s</string>
    <string name="m1be_2">\"I mean you no harm\!\"</string>
    <string name="m1be_3">Stand strong, you could take it on!</string>

    <string name="m1beDeath">The footsteps get faster and louder until the sheer bass of each
    thud makes you want to be sick! Out of the shadows charges a beast that can only have come
    from a nightmare. You attempt to run but it has already caught up. In one swift stomp your
    story has come to an end. Embarrassingly, you didn\'t even make it out of the first room.</string>

    <string name="Track_2_1_1_3_0">You start to walk towards the light in the distance. You notice
    that you have very little grip on the ground and will have to watch your step to avoid falling.
    A rhythmic thudding echoes from behind you, getting louder. You probably don\'t want to be here when
    whatever it is gets here.</string>

    <string name="Track_2_1_1_3_1">Keep walking towards the light</string>
    <string name="Track_2_1_1_3_2">Start to run</string>
    <string name="Track_2_1_1_3_3">Scream for help</string>

    <string name="m1beRun">Despite your better judgement, you start to run! For about 3 steps, it works brilliantly. However, on the
    fourth step your grip fails you, and you fall painfully to the ground. You may be able to get away still&#8230;</string>

    <string name="m1ge">The footsteps get faster and louder until the sheer bass of each
    thud makes you want to be sick! Out of the shadows charges a beast that can only have come
    from a nightmare. You\'ll never make it out. You sit and make peace with your last moments&#8230;</string>

    <string name="m1ge2">With a flash of light and a deafening explosion, you are momentarily blinded. Are you dead? After a few
    seconds you reopen your eyes to see the giant beast laying in front of you. You have no idea whether it is dead
    or merely knocked out, but you know that somebody or something must have caused this. Perhaps somebody heard your
    screaming?</string>

</resources>
